# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)

Puzzle.create(question: "Gloves for baby cats", solution: "kittens mittens", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A filthy, small flying animal", solution: "dirty birdy", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A rude Scottish girl", solution: "sassy lassie", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "Worthless coins", solution: "funny money", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A happy round juicy grape", solution: "merry berry", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A soft shaky stomach", solution: "jelly belly", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "Goofy William", solution: "silly Billy", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A scary bright flash you see during a storm", solution: "frightening lightning", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A happy flying elf", solution: "merry fairy", number_of_syllables: 2)
Puzzle.create(question: "A party at a convent", solution: "num fun", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "A married rodent", solution: "mouse spouse", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "An earthquake on a Sunday morning", solution: "church lurch", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "A hip monster", solution: "cool ghoul", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "A bashful insect", solution: "shy fly", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "A chubby kitty", solution: "fat cat", number_of_syllables: 1)
Puzzle.create(question: "Sexy but naive", solution: "quixotic erotic", number_of_syllables: 3)
Puzzle.create(question: "A meaner ring maker", solution: "crueler jeweler", number_of_syllables: 3)
Puzzle.create(question: "Legal documents about a nightclub with dancers", solution: "cabaret attache", number_of_syllables: 3)
Puzzle.create(question: "A kitchen utensil for a vampire", solution: "dracula spatula", number_of_syllables: 3)